<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>KUMAR ABHINAV on My Page </title>
    <link>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/</link>
    <description>Recent content in KUMAR ABHINAV on My Page </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II:Importance Of Education </title>
      <link>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/paper02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/paper02/</guid>
      <description>Education is a powerful weapon that aids an individual to face the adversities of life and overcome societal stigmas such as poverty, fear, status to achieve success. Education is the hope of development and success for most third-world countries and the world’s dominion countries. Mandatory education builds the scope of better growth and development.
Role of Education in India
Education has the potential to revolutionize the course of a nation – with skilled and educated youths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Technology in Our Daily Life - How Has Technology Changed Our Lives?</title>
      <link>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/aiml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 06:00:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/aiml/</guid>
      <description>No one can escape the absolute necessity of technology in our daily lives. Each of us is so heavily dependent on technology that we cannot do anything easily without it. Technology is important because it is used in all areas of life. When you contemplate your daily routine and count all the technology gadgets you consume in just one day, you will realize how important technology is when you use mobile, watch TV, drive a car, and use a computer or any electrical machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: Pollution</title>
      <link>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/paper01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/paper01/</guid>
      <description>Pollution is the process in which undesirable toxic contaminants contaminate our environment like air, water, soil, etc. It is creating sudden changes in the ecosystem, which is directly on indirectly leaving adverse effects on the lives of human beings, animals, and plants. It creates an imbalance in the natural system. Many things which are making our lives easy are harmful to the environment. For example, vehicles leave gases that pollute the air.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/atml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/post/atml/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://geekabhinav007.github.io/www/contact/</guid>
      <description>Always happy to hear from you.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   you can also mail me at abhinav26january@gmail.com .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
